FERNANDA TYROLA

 $n and a rita@hotmail.com/+1~(647)~836~8145\\ https://www.linkedin.com/in/fernanda-tyrola-6876322a/$

OBJECTIVE

I would like to improve my English knowledge and gain experience through an internship in a Canadian company, this includes gaining an insight into Canadian culture. I also intend to develop my KSOs and utilize it in favor of the organization. For this, I will learn fast using my communication and adaptability skills.

EDUCATION

September 2018	CENTENNIAL COLLEGE Certificate Program Communications and Media Fundamentals	Toronto, Canada
January 2018	CENTENNIAL COLLEGE Postgraduate Certificate Program Human Resources Management	Toronto, Canada
August 2015	CENTRO UNIVERSITARIO FIEO Postgraduate of Organizational Psychology	Sao Paulo, Brazil
August 2014	CENTRO UNIVERSITARIO FIEO Bachelor of Business Administration	Sao Paulo, Brazil

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov 2017 - May 2018

IMARKETING SOLUTIONS GROUP

Toronto, Canada

Call center Agent

- Answering two recorded calls at the same time.
- \$ 11,545 in donations between Nov 2017 to Feb 2018 with \$23.07 revenue per hour.

May 2012 - June 2016

BANCO BRADESCO S.A. (BANK)

São Paulo, Brazil

Risk Technician | Integrated Risk Control Department

- Developed reports and presentations on the organization's risk monitoring.
- Surveys and questionnaires on bank regulation.
- Implementing risk control and capital allocation of more than R\$ 600 billions, execution and effectiveness of controls which assure acceptable risk levels in the organization's processes.
- Responsible for complying with the Brazilian Central Bank rules for risk management activities.

SKILLS

- Portuguese (first language) / English
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PPT) / MacOS / Adobe Photoshop / Adobe Premiere
- SAP (Systems, Applications and Products in Data Processing)